<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
  <identifier>tarzanjpsoundtrack</identifier>
  <mediatype>audio</mediatype>
  <collection>opensource_audio</collection>
  <creator>Walt Disney Records and Edgar Rice Burroughs, Inc.</creator>
  <date>1999</date>
  <description>I know song 7 on this soundtrack receives flack from true Phil Collins fans but I got this album from Discogs to preserve lost recordings. &lt;div&gt;I think the reason why a new backing track was made for song 7 is because they wanted the end title to end in the same key as the movie version.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Either that or because the dubbing studio in Japan didn't have access to the backing track for Phil's original recording. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;But if you want song 7 to be somewhat the same as Phil's original recording, you can download the song and put it into a website that transposes recordings.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Once you have it in the website, transpose it up a half step so the opening key is Gb/F# instead of F. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Alternatively, you can wait for me to upload what I call version 2.0&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Version 2.0 of this soundtrack includes two additional songs and an improved version of song 7 which I will reveal when I upload that.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Regardless, we have reused recordings from the English soundtrack.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Songs 4 and 9-12 are reused from the English soundtrack and thankfully, the yell was left in for song 13.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Here's the track list for the TARZAN Soundtrack in Japanese.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Two Worlds - Marsa Sakamoto&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You’ll Be in My Heart - Fujita Toshiko &amp;amp; Marsa Sakamoto&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Son of Man - Marsa Sakamoto&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Trashin’ the Camp - Rosie O’Donnell, Phil Collins &amp;amp; Cast - TARZAN&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Strangers Like Me - Marsa Sakamoto&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Two Worlds (Reprise) - Marsa Sakamoto&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You’ll Be in My Heart (End Title) - Marsa Sakamoto&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Two Worlds (End Title) - Marsa Sakamoto&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;A Wondrous Place (Score) - Mark Mancina &amp;amp; Phil Collins&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Moves Like an Ape, Looks Like a Man (Score) - Mark Mancina &amp;amp; Phil Collins&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The Gorillas (Score) - Mark Mancina &amp;amp; Phil Collins&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;One Family (Score) - Mark Mancina &amp;amp; Phil Collins&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Two Worlds (Finale) - Marsa Sakamoto&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
  <language>jpn</language>
  <scanner>Internet Archive HTML5 Uploader 1.7.0</scanner>
  <subject>TARZAN</subject>
  <title>TARZAN ターザン (An Original Walt Disney Records Soundtrack)</title>
  <subject>Soundtrack</subject>
  <subject>Japanese</subject>
  <subject>Phil Collins</subject>
  <subject>Marsa Sakamoto</subject>
  <subject>Disney</subject>
  <uploader>jhmilsark@gmail.com</uploader>
  <publicdate>2026-04-06 03:53:13</publicdate>
  <addeddate>2026-04-06 03:53:13</addeddate>
  <curation>[curator]validator@archive.org[/curator][date]20260406040559[/date][comment]checked for malware[/comment]</curation>
</metadata>
